it is now time for tonight's hashtag
Wars K Kenny I thought my son's
saxophone recital was too
short Nick if you spend more money on
Froot Loops than you do on
rent Point Marin I've been watching a
honey booa
Marathon that is
deep
scary my mom's 40 minute story about her
cat was
fascinating Nick if you thought Avatar
was a
[Laughter]
[Applause]
documentary Marin my fingers taste like
chicken but my thumb
tastes
fud I wish we had more time to get the
details of that story
Rob hubo kale fornication yes
points Lon they're walking not driving
death you
community come on no come on fine take
them all away take them take all your
points away I don't care wipe them clean
you're going to care if I take all your
points away don't take okay well not
take point away uh Lennon just the 10
Prius 10 PRI oh just the 10 of us yeah
it's fun no I that's older demographic
yes yes yes Rob Hil CSI I think we can
recycle this guys yes
[Applause]
boys Brandon y Mama Mia Point points f
she Annie Get Your Gat points points
Andy daily Mary popping a cap in a
motherucker point for sure yes paer the
scissor up King
points yes TV Andy Dy How to Succeed in
Business by executing Biggie
Smalls the look of shock on your own
face Brandon Jesus Christ Superstar fun
Andy daily long day journey into sug
Knight you're very focused on that case
points Brandon Johnson best little hor
house in Compton yes
nice uh Steve in office colonoscopy day
yes points April bring your teenage
daughter's daughter to
work sensitivity training bra
[Applause]
day I don't all right yeah I can't with
the crowd I'll give you points I don't
know what it means I'll give you points
Tom uh bring your grandma to twerk day
points oh man Tom Lyon came to play nice
April um take your secretary to Hooters
day yeah yeah that would be not a good
one yeah Point Steve shut the up about
your kids for one fcking day
[Applause]
Linda